Guide to the Stanford University Architectural Collection SC1043
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Architectural drawings
  - Maples Pavilion, 09-300 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Roscoe Maples Pavilion
  - Maples Pavilion, 09-300 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Area development scheme - Roscoe Maples Pavilion and vicinity showing circulation parking and land use
  - Deguerre Pools and Courts, 09-310 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Stanford Department of Athletics Master Plan (DeGuerre pools and courts)
  - Deguerre Pools and Courts, 09-310 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Athletic development
  - Commissary, 09-400 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Site plan “A”, “B”, and “C” central food services
  - Commissary, 09-400 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Central Food Service Building
  - Commissary, 1969; 09-400 (Box map case Nd1)
    Architect: Clark, Stromquist and Potter
  - Commissary, 1987; 09-400 (Box map case Nd1)
    Architect: Formatech Design Inc.
    Description: Mezzanine system for Central Food Service Building
  - Stadium, 09-500 (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Stanford Athletics Facilities - Master Plan--[includes more than the stadium]
  - Stadium, 1972; 09-500 (Box map case Nd1)
    Architect: Hawley and Peterson
    Description: Stadium improvements
  - Stadium, 1991; 09-500 (Box map case Nd1)
    Architect: Eventures
    Description: Site plan and section/end views for Centennial Spectacular held at the stadium, 1991
  - Escondido Village Multipurpose Facility (Escondido V), 10-180 (Box map case Nd2)
  - Stanford Campus Recreational Facility [SCRA], 1966 Mar 8; 10-350 10-360 (Box map case Nd2)
    Architect: Royston Hannamoto Mayes and Beck
    Description: Landscape plans (plant list and staking plans)
    Format: prints
  - Cowell Student Health Service, 10-700 (Box map case Nd2)
    Description: Stanford University - Student Health Service Building
  - Durand House, 11-260 (Box map case Nd2)
    Architect: Hodges, C.E.
    Description: Front and side elevation of campus residence--Tentatively identified as the Durand house
  - President’s residence, 1919; 11-320 (Box map case Nd2)
    Architect: Clark, A. B.
    Description: Residence for Mrs. Lou Henry Hoover, Reservoir Drive. elevations and miscellaneous details
    Format: photostatic copies of blueprints
  - President’s residence, 1919; 11-320 (Box map case Nd2)
    Description: Residence for Mrs. Lou Henry Hoover, Reservoir Drive. Floor plans, elevations and architectural details. September 17, 1919
    # of Drawings: 22
  - President’s residence, 1919; 11-320 (Box map case Nd2)
    Description: Residence for Mrs. Lou Henry Hoover, Reservoir Drive. Structural engineering plans. T. Ronneberg, structural engineer. June 5, 1919
  - President’s residence, 1919; 11-320 (Box map case Nd2)
    Description: Residence for Mrs. Lou Henry Hoover, Reservoir Drive. Plumbing, heating, and electric plans. June 20, 1919
  - Hanna House, 1997; 11-330 (Box Basement MC)
    Architect: Architectural Resources Group
    Description: Hanna House Seismic Upgrade
    # of Drawings: 54
  - Hanna House, 1990; 11-330 (Box rolled)
    Architect: Forell/Elsesser Engineers
    Description: Hanna House Seismic Repair Design Development
    Format: copies (some fading)
  - Pearce Mitchell Houses, 1974; 11-500 (Box map case Nd2)
    Description: Faculty apartment project - Stanford University
  - Semi-Detached Houses, 1900; 11-xxx (Box C2)
    Description: Proposed Semi-Detached Houses to be Erected at the Leland Stanford Jr. University. 2 floor plans, 1 roof plan, and 1 site map for Yost/Mirrielees house on Lasuen.
  - Five Houses for Mrs. Hoover, 1924; 11-xxx (Box rolled)
    Architect: Clark, A. B
    Description: Plot plan, floor plans, and elevations for 5 houses designed as low-cost housing for junior faculty members. undated [probably 1924]
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 1962 Oct 3; 12-xxx (Box A1)
    Description: SLAC - auditorium-cafeteria combining
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 12-xxx (Box A1)
    Description: Two-mile linear electron accelerator
    Format: Photographs of model and sketch
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 1977; 12-xxx (Box not specified)
    Description: SLAC Master Plan Oct. 21, 1977. With color coding for existing buildings and future buildings
    Format: Printed with added color, 41 x 23 in.
  - Palo Alto Hospital [Hoover Pavilion], 1946; 13-100 (Box D1)
    Architect: Clark, Birge M.
    Description: Proposed Additions and Alterations. Includes plot plan; floor plans (1-6); and elevations.
    Format: blueline print
  - Nurses Home (SUMC ?), 13-110 (Box map case Nd3)
    Description: Nurses Home
  - Mausoleum, 13-xxx (Box C2)
    Architect: Potter, William A.
    Description: Plans, Elevations and Sections for a Tomb for the Hon. Leland Stanford.--[note on cover states “the way it wasn’t built”]
    Format: ink and watercolor on linen, bound with paper cover
  - Faculty Field Club House, 1920; 13-xxx (Box map case Nd3)
    Description: Faculty club elevations and floor plans. Signed by G. H. Marx (president) and A. B. Clark (treasurer), undated. L. S. Bean contractor. ca. 1920
    Format: Linen
    Status: Destroyed
  - Faculty Field Club House, 1960; 13-xxx (Box map case Nd3)
    Description: Faculty club - proposed remodel for Naval Science.
    Format: diazo
  - Central Steam and Chilled Water Plant, 14-100 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Steam plant
  - Central Energy Facility, 1976 Dec 22; 14-100 (Box map case Nd4)
    Architect: Spencer Associates
    Description: Central Energy Facility Master Plan 1977 Sheet 1 [shows existing buildings, master planning area, additions for 1977]
    Format: diazo print
  - George Vanderbilt Foundation, 1959 May 28; 14-620 (Box B2)
    Description: Warehouse compound of George Vanderbilt Foundation on Searsville Rd, and George Vanderbilt Foundation development plan [Bleaker House]
    Format: ink and colored pencil on paper
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Living room J. Henry Meyer Reisdence, [#40]
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: First Floor Plan [#48A]
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Brick Work on Terrace and Steps [#64]--(2 copies, one is damaged)
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: South Elevation [#71]
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Entrance Elevation, Scheme 1 [#72A]--Entrance Elevation, Scheme 2 [#72B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: First Floor Plan (Latest) [#76]
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Second Floor Plan (Latest) [#77]
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Basement Plan (Final) [#78]
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Typical Cornice for Lilving Room, Dining Room, Library and Stair Halls [#79]
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Second floor J. Henry Meyer residence [#88]
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: First floor J. Henry Meyer residence [#89]
  - Meyer-Buck House, [1920]; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Basement J. Henry Meyer Residence [#90]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Mar 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Living Room J. Henry Meyer Residence [#42B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Mar 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Interiors J. Henry Meyer Residence [#42A]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Mar 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: East and West Elevations [#43A, B, C]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Mar 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: South Elevation [#44A, B, C]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Mar 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: North Elevation [#45A, B, C]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Mar 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: 1/4 “ and 3/4 “ scale sections [#60]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Mar 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Roof Plan [#46A, B, C]--(#46A is damaged and has been foldered separately)
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Mar 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Basement Plan [#83]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Mar 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Second floor plan [#47B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Mar 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Sections J. Henry Meyer Residence [#85]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Apr 5; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Details of Construction of Main Roof [#67]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Apr 7; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Detail of Base of Bay Windows [#70]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Apr 10; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Plan of Framing, First Floor [#68]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Apr 12; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Plan of Framing, Second Floor [#69]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jun 21; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Detail of Revised Windows where Quoins Occur [#57A, B, C]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jul 8; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Revised Chimney Tops [#50]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Apr 28; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Brickwork for Chimney [#87]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 May 6; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Framing for Balconies [#73]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jun 1; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Elliptical Sash [#58A, B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jun 5; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Door and Sidelight in Lavatory (first floor) [#59A, B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jun 7; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Locations of radiators in library [#54A, B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jun 8; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Detail of Entrance Vestibule [#61]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jun 12; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Detail of Library [#65A, B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jun 15; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Detail of Quoinson Main - One and Two Story Wings [#56A, B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jun 15; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Detail of Interiors [#74A, B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jul 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Detail of Cases [#82]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jul 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Detail of Lattice on Terrace and North Elevation [#41A, B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jun 16; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Interior Details [#75A, B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jul 9; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Cases J. Henry Meyer Residence [#80]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jul 12; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Cabinets in Butler’s Pantry [#51]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jul 12; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Case Details [#55]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jul 14; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Revised Base J. Henry Meyer Residence [#81A, B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Jul 29; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Garden Layout [#62]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920-08-26; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Paneling over Mantel in Library [#91]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Aug 31; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Supply cases, basement [#52]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Aug 27; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Door Jambs [#84]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Sep 7; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Second floor cases [# 53]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Sep 8; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Linen Room [#63]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920-09-17; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Library Cases [#66]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1920 Oct 4; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Revised vents, servants’ wing [#49A, B]
  - Meyer-Buck House, 1949 Nov 29; 14-900 (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Ore Electric Push Button Central Residence Elevator [#86]
  - Concrete Shell Structure, 1962 May 9; 14-xxx (Box C2)
    Description: Experimental concrete shell structure on Searsville Road. One site plan and three sketches of structure.
    Format: blueprint; photocopies (3)
  - Jordan Quad Parking Lot, 1963 Feb 8; 14-xxx (Box B2)
    Description: Location plan - compact stall marking Jordan Quad parking lot
    Format: pencil and ink on paper
  - Portage Road Warehouse, 90-946R (Box map case)
    Description: Purchasing and stores warehouse - Portage Road Warehouse [might be 09-110 Procurement Stores]
  - Double House A at Stanford University, undated; Residential (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: includes foundation; first and second floors; front, side and rear facades
  - Double House B at Stanford University, undated; Residential (Box map case Nd5)
  - Double House C at Stanford University, undated; Residential (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: 2 sets: includes foundation; first and second floors; front, side and rear facades; interior details
    Format: ink on linen; blueprint
  - Double House D at Stanford University, undated; Residential (Box map case Nd5)
    Architect: Thompson, William (may not be architect)
  - Double House D at Stanford University, undated; Residential (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Sleeping porch addition to double house D
  - Residence to be built for the president, circa 1892; Residential (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: includes front, side and rear elevations; 1st and 2nd floor plans; roof and attic plan; foundation; arch in main hall
  - Durand House (aka Kirkman House), 1905; residential (Box Basement MC)
    Description: Architectural drawings for Durand House, ca. 1905
    Format: ink on paper; blueprint
  - Prefabricated Building, TM5-9611 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Prefabricated Building TM5-9611 (building razed in 1946)
  - Interim Building for Research Mathematical Sciences, 1960 Nov 16 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Interim office building for Research Mathematical Sciences: proposals A,B, C
  - Service Station Building (razed), 1938 Jan 12 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: BMT
    Description: Service station building - Stanford campus (razed)
  - Panama and Duena Streets Site Development, 1968 Apr 8 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Schematics for site development near Panama and Duena Streets
  - Panama Street, 1977 Aug 20 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Scheme for improving PanamaStreet
  - Parking Lot “J”, 1975-02 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Architect: Brian, Kangas, Foulk and Associates
    Description: Parking Lot “J” expansion
  - Stanford Band Stand, 1916 (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Stanford Band Stand Proposal
    Format: tissue paper
  - Stanford Band Stand (Box map case Na8-10)
    Description: Band Stand for Stanford Univ.
  - Stanford Band Stand (Box map case Na8-10)
    Format: encapsulated plans
  - Hoover Library Group, Oct. 14, 1930 (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Sketch for proposed food research, war memorial, and Hoover Library Group
    Format: pencil and colored pencil on paper; encapsulated
  - New Quad (Hoover bldgs) (Box map case Na11-15)
    Description: Proposed layout of New Quadrange (Food Research, War Memorial, and Hoover Library group)--stored as Q3 but could also be Q6
    Format: one is framed
  - Parking Areas (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Existing parking areas for Encina, Crothers Memorial, Eating Clubs, Toyon and Branner
  - Parking Areas (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Proposed parking areas for Encina, Crothers memorial, Eating clubs, Toyon, and Branner
  - Wilbur Lot (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Scheme 1: Remodelled Wilbur Lot
  - Arguello Street service roads (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Study for service roads, Arguello Street alignment
  - Parking Lot (Box map case Na18)
    Description: Plan for interim parking lot to serve Branner, eating clubs (relocated), and Toyon
  - Chemistry Annex - Assay Laboratory (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Chemistry Annex - Assay laboratory
    Status: Razed 1960
  - Technical Science Quad, 1949-05-29 (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Technical Science (Quad) proposal - Schemes 1 and 2; Schemes A and B
  - Technical Science Quad (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Technical science quad
  - 12-KV Substation (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Location and site of proposed 12-KV substation--Could also be quad 02-560
  - Chemistry Quad (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Development plan for Chemistry Quad, building sites, circulation and parking and planting areas
  - Chemistry Quad (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Preliminary plan for lot “D” chemistry quad - parking additions
  - Stanford Medical Center parking (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Schematic drawing showing location and number of proposed parking areas, Stanford Medical Center
  - Medical Center (Box map case Na19)
    Description: Road improvement, Medical Center fire lane
  - Parking Lot “H” (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Improvement plans for parking lot “H”
  - Serra Street parking (Box map case Nd1)
    Description: Parking extending along Serra from Salvez Street to Lasuen Mall
  - Escondido Village (Box map case Nd2)
    Description: Buildings 1-238
  - Stanford Married Student Housing - High Rise Apartments (Box map case Nd2)
    Description: buildings 63, 74, 87, 102, 109, 119, 126, 145
  - Hoskins House parking (Box map case Nd2)
    Description: A scheme to provide additional Hoskins House parking for visitors
  - Faculty and staff housing (Box map case Nd2)
    Description: Site study for medium-density housing for faculty and staff
  - Faculty Field Club House (Box map case Nd3)
    Description: Faculty field club house (burned down)
  - Arboretum, 1923 (Box map case Nd3)
    Description: Arboretum plant guide; see SC168 or SC195 for Dailey’s planting key
  - Oval - U.G. parking structure (Box map case Nd3)
    Description: The Oval - U.G. -- Parking structure (to repair)
  - Parking lots F and G (Box map case Nd3)
    Description: Proposed parking lots F and F, vicinity of Palm Drive and the Oval
  - Computation Center (Box map case Nd4)
    Description: Computation center
  - School of Dentistry, 1936 Jul 21 (Box B2)
    Description: College of Physicians and Surgeons, School of Dentistry
  - Cooper Medical College (Box C2)
    Architect: Wright and Sanders
    Description: Cooper Medical College extension - Lane Hospital, San Francisco - fourth floor plan
  - Cooper Medical College (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Cooper Medical College extension San Francisco (Lane Hospital)
  - Santa Barbara Seismological Station (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Detail of housing for seismograph and chronograph; Santa Barbara Station; building for a seismological station
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Electrical work - plans and details - Linear Acceleration Lab
  - [multiple campus buildings] (Box B2)
    Description: Elevation drawings of a variety of campus buildings, undated and unsigned
  - [multiple campus buildings], 1954 Feb 10 (Box A1)
    Description: Existing and definitely planned buildings
  - [exhibition gallery] (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: A gallery for the exhibition of paintings
  - Albers Wall, 1974-1977 (Box map case Nd5)
    Architect: Ellwood Associates
    Description: Brick face elevations and details; granite face elevations and details
  - Kellogg Foundation Center (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Kellogg Foundation Center
  - Landscaping (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: The LSJU - Landscaping [6/98 not found in drawer in 341 map case]
  - Mineral engineering building (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Mineral engineering building
  - Natural Science Buildings, undated (Box C2)
    Description: Natural science buildings--[cross section; possibly of quad building]
    Format: photographic copy
  - Military training department (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Office building for military training department at LSJU
  - Dibble General Hospital, 1943 (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Palo Alto General Hospital Automatic sprinkler system plot plan
  - Linear Acceleration Laboratory (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Linear Acceleration Laboratory
  - General Telephone and Electronics Laboratories (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Palo Alto laboratories of General Telephone and Electronics Laboratories, INc. (off Arastradero Road)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Planting legend - SLAC
  - Stanford Library (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Preliminary CPM for Stanford Library [unspecified]
  - Biological Labs, Dec. 1927 - Jan. 1928 (Box B2)
    Description: Preliminary Sketches Biological Laboratories (Scheme A, B, and C) - elevations and floor plans
  - Bicycle Shop (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Proposed bicycle shop relocation - site plan
  - School of Denistry, 1936 Mar 9 (Box B2)
    Description: Proposed Memorial School of Dentistry. Artist’s rendering.
    Format: photographic copies (one neg, one positive)
  - Microwave Lab (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Radiation vault microwave lab, Stanford--[possibly same as 04-250]
  - [multiple campus buildings], circa 1962 (Box A1)
    Architect: [Planning Office]
    Description: remodeling of stone buildings--[campus map with info on date and amount of remodeling]
  - Unidentified (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: remodeling of stone buildings
  - Physiology Research labs, 1928 Jan 27 (Box B2)
    Description: Preliminary Sketches Research Laboratories General Physiology, (scheme D). Floor plans (includes vivarium)
  - Lane Hospital (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Lane Hospital
  - Lane Hospital (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Lane Hospital, San Francisco
    Format: cloth
  - Lane Hospital (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Sub-basement / basement plans - Lane Hospital, San Francisco
  - Lane Hospital and Stanford Medical School, 1910 (Box A1)
    Description: Lane Hospital and Stanford Medical School. Sub-basement and first floor plans
  - Stanford Medical School (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Stanford Medical School
  - Lane Medical Library, 1911 Sep 13 (Box B2)
    Architect: Pissis, Albert
    Description: Lane Medical Library of Stanford University [in San Francisco]. Floor plans, elevations, one sheet of details. Includes one note re square foot totals.
    Format: photographic copies of originals
  - Stanford Medical School (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Stanford Medical School and vicinity (site plan?)
  - Stanford University Hospital, 1953 Sep 15 (Box B2)
    Description: Scheme “G” redevelopment of S. U. Hospitals at San Francisco
  - Stanford University Hospitals, 1950 Mar 10 (Box A1)
    Architect: Spencer and Ambrose; Talley and Lee
    Description: Extension of auxiliary fire alarm system - Stanford University Hospitals [in San Francisco]
  - Stanford Medical School (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Special survey of the Leland Stanford Jr., Hospital and College, San Francisco
  - Stanford Medical School, 1949 Jul 13 (Box C2)
    Description: Study of Stanford Medical School building, San Francisco
    Format: pencil on drawing paper
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: SLAC site plan
  - Unidentified (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Southern alignment of Burgess extension
  - Stanford Hospital (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Stanford Hospital, San Francisco
  - Stanford Medical School Library (Box map case Nd5)
    Description: Stanford Medical Library - Lane Hospital
  - Stanford Medical Center (Box map case)
    Description: Proposed additional bicycle parking, Stanford Medical Center
  - Stanford Village, circa 1948 (Box A1)